<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on W. T. Powell and the Empath Detective Mystery Series</title>
    <link>http://wtpowell.com/about/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on W. T. Powell and the Empath Detective Mystery Series</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 14:29:49 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://wtpowell.com/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>W. T. Powell - Empath Detective Mystery Series</title>
      <link>http://wtpowell.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 14:29:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://wtpowell.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The first-time and very amateur detective, Mark Falcon, is an empath. He feels people’s emotions. A lot. Which is usually quite painful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So he’s wound up as a broke, isolated web developer in the Shenandoah Valley of Virginia. (Where &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; I get these ideas?)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then he realizes he might be able to sense what a murder suspect is &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; feeling. At least … sometimes…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The story is told by Pete Villette, his soon-to-be bestish friend and housemate. Here’s the opening page:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I’m just going to start typing, because I can’t decide whether to start with the dead woman flying the glider, or when Mark first literally read my mind, or maybe that crazy creeptastic first funeral.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ugh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll be straight up, if solving murders actually paid anything, I wouldn’t be writing this whole ebook thing at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But we both missed a lot of work time getting mixed up in this, and I’m not going to say we’re desperate, but you can only eat so much rice before your Mom starts dropping eighty-pound hints about rickets. Let’s just say your purchase will make a real difference in a young man’s life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least I’m officially “out of the nest.” When some lunatic tries to murderize you, that’s got to count as some kind of transition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s the opening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is book 1 of an all-new mystery series I’m releasing in January on Amazon. If you’re in, I&amp;rsquo;d love you to read this 67,000 word draft over the next few weeks and share your feedback.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In return, you’ll get a free copy, a shoutout in the Acknowledgments, and my undying gratitude. For real. Plus, the thrill of being on the team that forges the next runaway bestseller series. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s the link. I basically just need you to fill in your email address so I can send you access to the book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.surveygizmo.com/…/Beta-Read-My-New-Mystery-Series&#34;&gt;http://www.surveygizmo.com/…/Beta-Read-My-New-Mystery-Series&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And if this isn’t your thing, maybe you know some avid mystery fan aching for their next hit of comedy/danger/romance/sleuthery? A share would be &lt;em&gt;awesome&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>